EXECUTIVE SUMMARY

More than 5 years' experience in handling Performance Management System (PMS) which indicate for individual performance or KPI. Works closely with senior managerial or directional staffs to provide administrative support for discretion and confidentiality. Able to garner a support from a staff and executive management, acting as a key of events and talent to consolidate a budget costing for traveling, events and meeting.



NOOR HERDAYU BTE JAINAL

Permanent Address: No 175, Jalan Tembusu 15,

Taman Bukit Rinting, 81750 Masai,

Johor Bahru, Johor.

Mobile number: +6013-7242210

E-mail: herdayu.jainal@yahoo.com

Nationality: Malaysian

 Identity Card No:
 820105 – 01 – 5844

 Date of Birth:
 5 January 1982

Gender: Female Marital Status: Married

EXPERIENCE

Edaran Otomobil Nasional Berhad (EON), Shah Alam Executive (EON Auto Mart) / Executive Secretary (Mitsubishi) Nov 2012 – Present

Current Salary: RM 3,000.00

- Provide administrative support to Chief Operating Officer (COO) EON Auto Mart in a timely and courtesy manner
- Ensuring all documents for COO EON Auto Mart approval is in compliance with Company's policy and within his limit of authority
- Assist COO EON Auto Mart to plan Branch Managers Key Performance Indicator
- Monitoring and manage Performance Management System (PMS) for branches and HQ personals in order to measure organization and individual performance
- Assist Human Capital Development Department in Recruitment process (Manpower requisition, Staff Welfare etc)

- Develop and compute budget for function/training prepared in advance with lowest cost possible, i.e usage of budget airlines, car pool, shared lodging
- Arrange for a manage material for COO EON Auto Mart's meetings with staff and relevant department which requires initiative and the ability to work to tight deadlines
- Set up and handled incoming mail and office filling systems
- Collected and coordinated the flow of internal and external information
- Monitor existing documents to ensure they remain thorough, accurate and upto-date
- Responsible for word processing collation of official company documents
- Reconcile expenses and general administrative duties

Edaran Otomobil Nasional Berhad (EON), Shah Alam Executive - Sales Operations / Executive Secretary (Proton) Jan 2008 – Oct 2012

- Assist GM Proton Operations to produce timely management reports covering all aspects of branch operations, effectiveness, efficiency and financial results
- Assist GM -Proton Operations to plan, organize and direct branch operations to ensure the achievement of performance standards objectives
- Monitoring the movement of documents, supplying and presenting with accurate information
- Ensuring all documents for GM Proton Operations approval is in compliance with Company's policy and within his limit of authority
- To organize and plan meeting/traveling between GM Proton Operations and relevant department
- Develop effective relations with internal, external, business association and customers
- Develop and compute budget for function/training prepared in advance with lowest cost possible, i.e usage of budget airlines, car pool, shared lodging
- To ensure that branch's planned activities and operations can be conducted in the most efficient way
- Assist GM Proton Operations to plan Branch Managers Key Performance Indicator
- Monitoring and ensure branches compliance of SOP
- Assist GM Proton Operations to establish branches AMP

Edaran Otomobil Nasional Berhad (EON), Shah Alam On-job Training (OJT) Jan 2007 – Apr 2007

<u>Performance Management System (PMS) Administration</u>

- Assist the PMS Team Members in administering and maintaining the performance management system
- Update the Employees' data and staff movement into electronic PMS for EON Group of Companies
- Analyze the Performance Management data/ outcome to identify and interpret trends in areas that are beneficial to the companies
- To maintain effectives filing system for the performance management data.
- To update staff movement as and when required by users

• Update existing and changes in JCM to reflect changes in EON working environment

Compensation and Benefit (C & B)

- Involved in the Compensation and Benefit review for EON Group of Companies.
- Prepare C & B summary for the management decision

Training

 Assist Learning and Development Department to coordinate training programs at EON Head Office

Reason of leaving - End of practical training period

EDUCATION AND QUALIFICATIONS_

2004 – 2006	Universiti Teknologi MARA (UiTM), Shah Alam, Selangor Darul Ehsan Bachelor of Science, Management Mathematics CGPA 2.97
2001 – 2004	Universiti Teknologi MARA (UiTM), Shah Alam, Selangor Darul Ehsan Diploma, Science Quantitative CGPA 3.19
2000 – 2001	Universiti Teknologi MARA (UiTM), Shah Alam, Selangor Darul Ehsan Certificate, Information Technology CGPA 2.67

PERSONAL STRENGTHS AND SKILLS

Personal attributes:

- Accuracy | Excellent organizational skills | Planning and Time Management
- Gregarious | Optimistic | Initiative | Reliability | Stress tolerance
- Ready for taking challenging roles in an immense and complex organization
- A positive person and cheerful to others
- Fast learner and committed towards achievement goals and objectives
- A good team player

Languages:

- Malay Language (Very Good)
- English (Good)
- Mandarin (Intermediate)

Core Knowledge and Functional Skill Areas:

- Have a very good knowledge in computer system
- In depth knowledge of Microsoft Office Ms Word, Excel, Access and Power Point
- Relevant experience in software applications such as MATLAB, SPSS, ARENA and Microsoft Project
- A computer savvy

Expected Salary: RM 3,700 (negotiable)

REFEREES

En. Abdul Wahab Mohd Noor

Ex COO – EON Auto Mart No 2, Persiaran Bandar Baru Tambun 6, Bandar Baru Tambun. Ipoh

Telephone: 012-5268999

E-mail: <u>wahab nor@yahoo.com</u>